

## WHO I AM

I'm a front-end developer who really enjoys designing creative and robust solutions to many kinds of problems.

As I am also an economist, I like to find the perfect mix between design and efficiency. I am a lifelong learner.

With over 10 years in the financial sector, especially corporate finance, and a couple of years teaching economics, I have tons of experience as a team player and storyteller.

In my personal opinion, it is very important to be part of a group that promotes diversity and respect. In that sense, **empathy** is the word and the action that best defines me.

### SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React
- Poact Na
- Tailwind
- Soft Skill
- Git
- GitHub
- Inglés B1

## PROUD OF

- Cum Laude mention in both Bachelor in Economics and MA in Economics
- author of <u>working papers</u> published in international peer reviewed journal.
- I make my own pasta for myself and friends at least once a week. We love it!

## CONTACT

ferrelli.mazza@gmail.com





# FEDE MAZZA

FRONT END DEVELOPER & ECONOMIST



## **EDUCATION**

- CODO A CODO BOOTCAMP
   Full Stack Developer. 2021
- IBM Y CAC BOOTCAMP React Native. 2021
- UDEMY
   HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Resposive Design.
- ACCENTURE

  Soft Skills. 2021
- UNIVERSIDAD TECNOLOGICA NACIONAL Diploma in Business Intelligence. 2020
- UNIVERSIDAD CEMA MA In Economics, 2016
- UNIVERSIDAD UADE

  Bachelor degree in Economícs. 2012

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **HEAD OF FINANCE**

COL Supermarket. 2018 - Now

• In charge of economic-financial analisys team. Capital investment analysis. Working capital optimization.

#### **CHIEF OF TREASURY**

Cinesa, Barcelona. 2017-2018

• In charge of treasury team.

# **ECONOMIC-FINANCIAL ANALYST**

Corporación América . 2011-2016

• Analysis of a project's relevant economic factors in order to ascertain its convenience in sectors like airports, banking, oil, etc.